<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LearnFlux</string>
    <string name="shared_name">com.idesolusiasia.learnflux.lastsync</string>

    <!--font-->
    <string name="font_groups_grid">"fonts/arial-narrow.ttf"</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login and register -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="prompt_username">Username</string>
    <string name="prompt_firstname">First Name</string>
    <string name="prompt_lastname">Last Name</string>
    <string name="prompt_confirm">Confirm Password</string>

    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_register">Register</string>

    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_confirm">Passwords don\'t match</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>

    <string name="permission_rationale">"Some permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chat">Chat</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_event_chat">EventChat</string>
    <string name="remarks">Curabitur auctor tristique lobortis. Quisque bibendum, ipsum in feugiat pharetra, odio libero malesuada turpis, tempus fermentum augue est sit amet magna. Vestibulum bibendum lectus non mauris porta, sed blandit purus scelerisque.</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        LASALLE College of the Arts provides a supportive, progressive and truly inspiring
        environment for our students.
        \nWith a focus on nurturing creative expression, innovation and independence of thought,
        we encourage students to be inquisitive and original artists and designers.
        They become highly skilled, and excel both in their chosen specialisms and in their
        collaborations
        with practitioners from other disciplines.
    </string>
    <string name="mission_text">Curabitur auctor tristique lobortis. Quisque bibendum,
        ipsum in feugiat pharetra, odio libero malesuada turpis, tempus fermentum augue est sit amet
        magna. Vestibulum bibendum lectus non mauris porta, sed blandit purus scelerisque.
        Sed consequat mollis ornare. Sed laoreet id dolor vitae facilisis. Mauris varius orci sed
        turpis commodo mattis. Cras vel nibh scelerisque urna tincidunt vestibulum accumsan pharetra ex.
        Proin ullamcorper eros non justo tincidunt lobortis. Ut sapien nisi, bibendum tempor efficitur
        ultricies, pellentesque interdum diam. Aliquam commodo felis eu urna consectetur, ut semper diam
        tempor. Etiam eu maximus sapien, a tristique tortor.
    </string>
    <string name="large_text_1">
        LASALLE College of the Arts provides a supportive, progressive and truly inspiring
        environment for our students.
        \nWith a focus on nurturing creative expression, innovation and independence of thought,
        we encourage students to be inquisitive and original artists and designers.
        They become highly skilled, and excel both in their chosen specialisms and in their
        collaborations
        with practitioners from other disciplines.
        \nThe College prepares graduates for sustained and successful careers in the creative
        industries through
        a practice-based and industry-led pedagogy. It is a demanding and immersive learning
        experience guided
        by an outstanding international faculty, professional artists, and industry mentors.
        We foster high-level creative skills, but allow our students to assert their freedom to be
        different,
        and to chart imaginative new territories – and this is what prepares them for real and
        sustainable careers in the arts.
        \nWe offer an exceptional range of Diploma, Bachelors and Masters degree programmes that are
        well respected
        in the global arts arena. With a strategic and central location in Singapore\'s cultural
        district,
        our award-winning, open campus provides a magnificent space and inspirational setting for
        study and creative exchange.
        \nAt LASALLE College of Arts we work continually to innovate in our teaching and research,
        and to set new benchmarks in arts education. We believe in our students and their ability to
        be the pioneers
        who will help to define the future of contemporary arts practice.
    </string>
    <string name="goal">Curabitur auctor tristique lobortis. Quisque bibendum, ipsum in feugiat pharetra, odio libero malesuada turpis, tempus fermentum augue est sit amet magna. Vestibulum bibendum lectus non mauris porta, sed blandit purus scelerisque. Sed consequat mollis ornare. Sed laoreet id dolor vitae facilisis. Mauris varius orci sed turpis commodo mattis. Cras vel nibh scelerisque urna tincidunt vestibulum accumsan pharetra ex. Proin ullamcorper eros non justo tincidunt lobortis. Ut sapien nisi, bibendum tempor efficitur ultricies, pellentesque interdum diam. Aliquam commodo felis eu urna consectetur, ut semper diam tempor. Etiam eu maximus sapien, a tristique tortor.
</string>
    <string name="color_primary">#8BC34A</string>
    <string-array name="invitee_status">
        <item>Not Set</item>
        <item>Going</item>
        <item>Interested</item>
        <item>Not Going</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="BASE_URL">http://lfapp.learnflux.net/</string>
    <string name="BASE_URL2">http://lfapp2.learnflux.net/</string>
    <string name="URL_LOGIN">oauth/v2/token</string>
    <string name="client_id">
       580db5c83a603f82528b4567_ahqk6r8gni8088ock80wkkok4wk0ooc8g4s0kkg880soow4k8
    </string>
    <string name="client_secret">5d13jtr20js4wcw0488888ck0k0c0sk0kos8c08wo8wsgog8ss</string>
    <string name="URL_VERSION">v1/</string>
    <string name="URL_VERSION2">v1.1/</string>
    <string name="URL_ME">me</string>
    <string name="URL_FRIEND">me/friend</string>
    <string name="URL_MESSAGES">messages</string>
    <string name="URL_THREAD_MESSAGES">messages/%s</string>
    <string name="URL_REGISTER">register</string>
    <string name="URL_ORGANIZATIONS">groups</string>
    <string name="URL_EVENTS">events</string>
    <string name="URL_GROUP_PROFILE">groups/%s</string>
    <string name="URL_GROUP">groups</string>
    <string name="URL_POLL">poll</string>
    <string name="URL_IMAGE">image</string>

    //alert
    <string name="success_registration">You have successfully registered.
        Please allow some time for the system to process your registration.
        You will get notification on your email when your account has been activated. Thank you.
    </string>
</resources>
